Undertaste
vel yokai so beautiful!
Brands are too participating
Rear Expo Lace
Good work!
Thank you for your time
Best regards
thank you so much for this trip!
thank you so much!
I'm really happy
That's great.
You like the song?
It's coming.
It's so, so, so, so, so good.
It's great.
We were all half-crying when we heard it.
We all jumped up and down.
Really?
It's like, "You did it!
I'm so happy.
I'm just doing this on my own.
Stop it.
It's a one-time job.
This is my guitar.
I've never played one before.
Let's go inside.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry to bother you.
So, I brought all kinds of stuff.
So that we can get different sounds.
Let's go inside the instrument.
Great.
That's great.
Not even close!
We're in it together!
Thank you!
I've always had a lot of, you know, saxies, for example, and I've always had a lot to offer.
But I still leave it to you when I write it.
I mean, if you sing it like this...
I'm sure you have a melody or something.
I had never done that before, so I asked my manager for help.
I asked the manager if it was possible to work with him on that kind of thing.
I asked my manager if we could work together on something like that, and he said that he'd heard about it, so I asked him to let me do it.
I'm so grateful!
I was rather strict with him, you know.
But still...
I'm so disappointed!
Yes! If you say "Yes!
I'll go numb.
Okay, then.
I've got them singing a little song. You want to listen to it over here?
Zhou Main 0., Toba 0,
Ich vow not to dance, but I'll always do
Sing it.
The camor is cool.
Kamo! Cool!
Isn't it too cool?
I don't get it.
Camo!
CAMO!
Duck! Duck!
Duck!
They'll start singing.
And on and on.
That's what I'm talking about!
Instead of saying "Do," you should say "What kind of night" and then you'll say "Video.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you should do that.
You're stopping a little too much.
I think it should come out a little thicker.
Yes, ma'am.
This space makes me happy, too.
Thank you very much.
It's a little bit too luxurious.
I'm so happy.
I was very moved.
But I'm really happy, I'm really happy, I'm happy to sing with Inose-san
I'm happy to sing with ease
I've been practicing, but when I sing individually
I'm so happy to be able to sing like this.
I'm happy to sing like this
It's passionate.
I really put my heart and soul into it.
How much?
How much do you put into it?
You're fishing with everything you've got.
How do you put it in?
You.
I'm like...
This one?
How do you get it in?
Oh, this way.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
You don't have to sing it well.
It's so good.
Numahara was so energetic.
He's energetic and energized.
That's all I'm saying.
And you've got to sing well.
Let's just do our best.
Please do!
I have seen many hardships in the past, and there have been wonderful Gyanpare, member teams, etc., and I feel that the audience and Gyanpare have created a song that will hold hands as we move forward from here on out.
But I don't know that long history. We sang together on that stage every day, moved around together, and although the girls may have liked or disliked each other, we experienced pain and joy together.
So, when you sing, you don't have to be good at all.
I wanted the girls to sing with that image in their minds, even if they don't sing well.
I just want my friends and members to think about that when they are performing live.
Yes.
Then, please do your best.
Yes, please do.
Good luck.
Did you film it? Just now.
It was really good.
The theme of the song was that we all wanted to sing together,
That's right.
I guess so. The theme was to sing together,
We wanted to create many places where everyone could sing together,
And that's why they asked us to do it,
We are aiming for a live performance that is fun, but also makes you cry with joy,
That's what we wanted to do with this song.
I was watching from offstage during the big show,
Yes, so you can see them dancing hard from very close up.
And from the front and from the back,
I was impressed that even the children in the back were doing their best without letting up,
Kubo-san was in the first row, I think,
Kubo-san was in the first row and he was saying, "Hey, hey!
I was doing that, wasn't I? I didn't go to that side.
I was saying, "Yes, yes, yes, yes.
There are more amazing people on that side.
Yes, yes.
We're doing live shows together, so we're working hard.
Yes.
The audience is probably encouraged by their hard work,
Many of them are about the same age as us,
Seeing them like that, I thought, "This is great.
To have a night like this, to get through a night like this.
I have nothing to say.
The night is called Doran.
I don't know what it is, but...
I bet it's the same.
Wonderful.
There's nothing more to say.
It's true.
Can I just get one more?
I've had three good ones so far.
I'm a little biased towards individuality.
I'm the main one.
My own.
Can I do whatever I want with it?
Thank you very much.
Can I go in now?
Are you out of your mind? Are you watching the video?
Yang on.
Are you singing with your friend?
Okay, okay.
Can I do it?
I'm not gonna ask you what kind of nights you've had, what kind of nights you've been through.
I'm not gonna ask you what kind of nights you've had, what kind of nights you've survived, what kind of mornings you've had.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you. Thank you.
Diva, diva, diva.
That's nice.
Can I have it written down?
Because I'm pretty sure I'd like your personality better if you were here.
I'm so happy.
Okay, diva.
Diva!
Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Shalala, Shalala, Shalala, Shalala, Shalala, Shalala.
Great. That's great.
I have a feeling. I have a feeling he's coming.
They're opening up.
Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
You already know... you already know... you probably know...
He said he has a feeling they're coming.
OK, let's go.
I'm going to live
Sing, dance, laugh
What do you call it if you don't call it youth?
Bunny
Usagi-chan
Usagi-chan is a version with full of personality
A version with a lot of personality
Yes...
I don't understand.
What's the five-star version?
Yes, stop!
Thank you.
You're really singing and breathing.
You're really singing... and you're breathing... maybe you're sucking... but if you do it a few more times... you'll get the full hit.
I'm just going to sing a few more of those notes and I'll be fine.
We're done recording for the day, right?
Thank you for your hard work.
We'll do our best.
We'll see you tomorrow.
We all have different members, so we'll be using them today to entertain the audience.
It's going to be great! You should definitely look forward to it. It was really fun.
When Ueno came into the booth and said, "Come on," everyone got excited.
It'll brighten up your love life.
I'll do my best to make this a good one.
Six obligations.
I'm sure you're probably imitating me with the traffic jams and all.
I don't know if you're imitating me, but I'm singing my own song.
I'm going to sing it like it's my own song, and if I get it wrong, it's better that way.
Okay, please do the movie.
It's scarier, I promise.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Laugh, laugh, laugh... it's called youth...
Keep the dust from distorting.
It's great.
Can I have another one?
Can I have another?
Wait a minute... one more.
That was amazing.
It was like singing to the longest one.
The long one.
Longest one.
Like singing to it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How's your throat still? Is it okay?
Perfectly fine.
Then why are you doing that?
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, my God.
Meatballs.
It's in!
Hey, Tonachan!
I've always wanted to say that.
Imitating the first producer.
Tonachan! That's what she said.
I can't get Tonachan out of my head.
Cannon!
We're the same.
Cannon?
Cannon.
Or Cannon.
Can I ask you to do it?
Cannon.
Cannon!
That's great! That's great!
Thank you!
You don't have to take any more pictures of Cannon, do you?
Hey!
Can...
Can... Go!
Tay!
No, look at me! Look, look, look!
You made me smile.
Take care of me, too.
I'm counting on you! It's all of us now!
Cheer up!
Yes!
Yes! Yeah!
Wow!
Please give us a live creative smiley face version!
Yes!
Sayy!
Kippers?
Sayee!
The song that connects you!
It's good! It's good!
How's it going?
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Can I have just one more?
Yes!
Aren't you getting bored? I don't know...
I'm not bored!
No, just smile!
I'm still working, Mr. Gamperly!
I'm watching you, on camera!
Please do it!
Yes, sir! Go!
With the audience...
Imagine you're singing! Live!
Yes!
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!
That's fun, too.
That one's rusty, too, so that's fun.
Don't worry, it's this one...
No, no, no... do whatever you want.
Then, it's fun, right? I'm going to go in.
I'll go in.
Go to the "Boo-Bah-Shi"...
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you...
This is so good!
It's so good! It's so good!
It's so much fun.
Seven yesterday, six today.
Like I said yesterday.
There's so much individuality.
The truth is, when we all sing together.
But when we sing together, our individuality gets blurred.
But when we sing together...
You can see their faces.
I think we made a great recording.
Everyone practiced so hard.
Taking notes and so on.
I think it's important to be serious.
I thought it's important to be serious.
They said the music was great.
And they said the music was good.
That's why
It was the first time for us to experience something like this.
It was really interesting.
Having people sing for us.
It's great.
You should try it like this.
It was great to be able to do that.
It was great that you were able to do that.
It was great.
It was a good experience.
It was.
It's just, you know.
I walked into that booth, and I thought, "Wow, he's really going for it.
And Mr. Kubo was so nervous.
He was in the back the whole time.
Just telling a girl you're tired of being behind her all the time...
It makes me a little nervous.
I'm sweating down my back.
Thank you very much.
It was a good experience.
You're the best.
It was a lot of fun.
You know, you just go for it.
You can go as far and as fast as you want.
That's the special power, isn't it?
That's what he's teaching us directly.
He told me which way he was coming.
I'm so glad you're still here.
I'm so glad.
It was fun.
I think you'll probably like this one a lot.
It's a really good song.
It's really easy.
Happy!
I wish we could all singalong together.
I want to sing to the tension
In that place
Mr. J is going to sing to the members.
I want to sing to the members, that's what it means.
He told me that he wrote the song with a lot of meaning.
Even though we have been through a lot of hardships
But as a Gyanparee, we still have the same problems
We have the same problems and struggles
and the same struggles that we all face.
I feel that we have been and will continue to be together with the members
I feel that we have been and will continue to be together as a melon
I like that.
It's very Gyanparee-like.
I think you wrote the best song ever.
I'm going to sing it for the rest of my life.
But it was great.
Thank you very much.
YO!